[{
    "theme": "üí¢ Dolores y molestias",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "How do you say 'I feel fine'?",
            "answers": ["me siento bien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I don't feel well'?",
            "answers": ["no me siento bien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am sick' if you're a man?",
            "answers": ["estoy enfermo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you say if you're a woman and you are sick?",
            "answers": ["estoy enferma"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What would a doctor ask to know where it hurts?",
            "answers": ["d√≥nde le duele"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How would you say 'It hurts here' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["me duele aqu√≠"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you say in Spanish if you have a headache?",
            "answers": ["me duele la cabeza"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you say in Spanish if your arms hurt?",
            "answers": ["me duelen los brazos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'my eye hurts' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["me duele el ojo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you say in Spanish if your feet hurt?",
            "answers": ["me duelen los pies"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'throat'?",
            "answers": ["la garganta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'leg' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["la pierna"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'mouth' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["la boca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'shoulder'?",
            "answers": ["el hombro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'my shoulders hurt' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["me duelen los hombros"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'ear'?",
            "answers": ["la oreja"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'my ears hurt' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["me duelen las orejas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'nose'?",
            "answers": ["la nariz"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'stomach'?",
            "answers": ["el est√≥mago"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'eyes' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["los ojos"]
        }
    ]
}]
